## **Christopher Bibby**

10 Plaza Boulevard
Liverpool, L8 5RT
07743 427539 • <a href="mailto:christopher-bibby-940722124/">chris.g.bibby@gmail.com</a>
<a href="mailto:https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-bibby-940722124/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-bibby-940722124/</a>
Driving Licence • Own Car

#### **Personal statement**

I am a highly motivated and hardworking individual, with experience working in a variety of different environments and roles, mainly in working in analytical roles. I am currently studying data science in a Skills Bootcamp ran by HyperionDev gaining skills in coding in Python and Machine learning amongst other skills. I also have an MSc in Business Strategy at Lancaster University, for which I achieved a merit, having also completed a History degree at Lancaster University. I completed A-Levels in Maths, Economics, and History.

I have an analytical, numerate, and diligent approach to work and research and have traveled extensively, and have enjoyed meeting with people from different backgrounds and cultures.

### **Key Skills**

- Knowledge of coding in Python, Machine learning models, Data visualisation and Natural language Processing
- Good research capability and experience, with strong analytical skills
- Advanced problem solving and numeracy skills
- Proficiency in areas of Microsoft Office, including, Excel, Word, Teams, Streams, Visio and PowerPoint

### **Work History**

## Associate, Deloitte LLP, The Hanover Building, Corporation St, Manchester M4 4AH (Sept 2022 – Jan 2022)

Key responsibilities:

• To analyse and assess whether the IT controls of firms were adequate and prevented the risk of material misstatement in their financial accounts

# Process Analyst, Charities Trust Ltd., 20 Century Building, Tower Street, Liverpool L3 4BJ (Jan 2022 – Aug 2022)

Key responsibilities:

- To document processes by interviewing and mapping said process across the organisation
- To analyse said processes and assist in theorising and implementing improvements for them

# Intern, Garic Ltd., Kingfisher Park, Aviation Road, Bury BL9 8GD (Oct 2021 – Nov 2021) Key responsibilities:

- To aid the firm in developing an IT roadmap for the next 3-5 years, through consulting with internal and external stakeholders
- Secondarily to assist in research related to the firm's new growth strategy

# Assistant, Hill Dickinson LLP, No.1 St. Paul's Square, Liverpool, L3 9SJ (Jul 2018 – Aug 2018) Key results:

- Developed understanding of the UK legal system, especially regarding corporate and commercial law
- Developed skills in utilising online databases, such as Companies House

## **Christopher Bibby**

 Performed minute taking during meetings and developed my ability to recognise and condense key information accordingly

# Assistant, Dow Scofield Watts Corporate Finance Limited, 7400 Daresbury Park, Daresbury, Warrington, WA4 4BS (Aug 2016 – Aug 2016)

Key results:

- Developed research skills identifying key companies in a sector
- Developed understanding of market analysis techniques
- Developed Excel skills

#### **Education**

#### HyperionDev (Dec 2023 - March 2024)

I am currently undergoing a Skills Bootcamp in Data Science with HyperionDev. In this course I am studying coding Python, Machine learning models, Data visualisation and more

### Lancaster University (Sept 2017 – Sept 2021)

I have completed a BA History at Lancaster in which I achieved 2:2 honours. Following this, I finished a Masters in Strategy at Lancaster University of which I have achieved a merit.

#### Cardiff University (2016 – 2017)

1st year History degree, including a module in basic Japanese

#### Oundle School (2010 - 2015)

Pre-U

History – D3 (A equivalent)

A-Levels:

- Maths B
- Economics B

10 GCSEs, grade A\*-B, including Maths (A\*)

### **Volunteering**

#### Collections Volunteer, National Trust, Quarry Bank Mill (June 2016 – August 2016)

Key results:

- Nurtured a diligent approach to my work
- Hands-on experience cataloguing and handling fragile materials
- Developed appreciation of the importance of local culture and history

### Teaching Assistant, Glapthorn Church of England Primary School, Oundle (Oct 2014 - March 2015)

Key results:

- School Award for exemplary performance in community action
- Developed ability to deal with all types of children
- Developed teaching and leadership ability

#### **Hobbies & Interests**

I like to travel, and I have travelled extensively to Japan, Turkey, and Iceland. Previously I have travelled across Central America, Morocco, and Tanzania where, following some volunteering work, I climbed Kilimanjaro. I also have an Advanced Open Water Diving Qualification and last dived while on Holiday in Mauritius, but have also dived abroad in Egypt, Greece, the Caribbean, and the Maldives. I'm a member of the Liverpool F.C. supporters club and enjoy playing squash, tennis, skiing and I took up snooker during lockdown. As well as this I was also elected as the Treasurer for the anime society at Lancaster University.